[{"answer": "I can, Brian.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Can you hear me OK?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "That is absolutely correct.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "It's not a doomsday scenario.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What's the probability right now, Chad, if these charts are accurate of this doing a direct hit on New York City?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "We are stubborn and resilient but we know when we have to go.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Are they leaving?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I think it's let's get down to business.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "How would you describe the mood of people on the streets in New York right now?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, it's a very serious storm.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "What is the sense you're getting about the reality of this hurricane and in particular a direct hit on New York City?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Well, in a worse case scenario, 12 feet is possible.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Is that a likely prospect, do you think from everything you're now looking at?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Well, as a partner with New York City, Office of Emergency Management, of course, in the state of New York, the FEMA regions.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "What is your view from a military point of view?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "I'm going to have to leave there.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Yes, we have.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Have you been personally briefing him on Irene?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "There's going to impacts and, again, the hurricane center has said that this forecast track is pretty much not going to change.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Are you beginning to feel now that it's almost inevitable that New York City, for example, will take a direct hit?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know about that.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "I mean, not that anybody would possibly blame you for doing that, but some people are suggesting as a slight overreaction this time to make sure that that kind of thing couldn't possibly happen again?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "I think, really, the concern in New York City is going to be how much storm surge we get.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Is it structural damage or is it from potential flooding?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's a decision that's case by case.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "For people not in those sections, is it sensible now to be thinking about getting out of there if you can?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Well, again, I look at this and what the team here has worked for to get ready.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Do you feel like you're on top of it?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Well, when we talk about disasters and we'll just talk about what government is doing when you do have disasters that are declared by the president, it is paid for by the U.S. taxpayers.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "How does this work?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "UGATE: Yes, I do.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Are you getting encouraging signs that evacuation and so on are being taken up by New Yorkers?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think that they take things seriously.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Professor Coch, you think that maybe New Yorkers having been through so much may not be that keen to evacuate?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "My gut feeling it won't be as bad because I think the storm will start as it starts to shear as it moves over the colder water, because it's not moving fast enough.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "What is your gut feeling from everything you've been hearing?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "If you're living under an altitude of 30 feet, yes.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Finally, if you would give me a one word answer -- if you're in New York now, should you leave?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "I can hear you, Piers.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Brian, can you hear me and what is going on now?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, you know it's exhilarating and frightening at the same time.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "What does it feel like right now, for you, standing in the middle of this thing?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I think they are going have a lot of problems.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "What would you imagine would happen there?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Piers, with everything I know right now -- again, this is a storm that because we haven't had anything like this in New York City, New York City needs to take seriously, and indeed it does.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "What's your take on it, with everything you knowing right now?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "If you were in New York right now, would you leave the city?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Well, I think what makes this storm really scary is just the population density on the East Coast.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What is your reading of what we're witnessing here with Hurricane Irene?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I would probably get out a topographic map and draw a line where there is probably 25 to 30 feet and stay higher than that.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "If you were in the city now, would you leave?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Right now, Piers, what's happening is that the window for preparation time is really coming to a close, as we anticipate the arrival of Irene.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "What can you tell me what's is going on right now in your state?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "'MALLEY: People are absolutely right to be concerned about this.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Are people right to be as concerned as they are sounding?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Well, it could happen, Piers.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Are you fearing a similar kind of catastrophe that we saw in Katrina, if this hits New York?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I think government certainly has changed.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Do you think lessons have been learned enough to prevent anything like Katrina happening again?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "But if there is a direct hit on somewhere like New York City, this is going very serious, isn't it?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "The simple answer, Piers, is yes.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "What is the simple answer?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Well, I would say this, Piers.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "If the hurricane hits somewhere like New York, and there is substantial damage and lots of flooding and so on, if you're safe, is it better to stay off the cell phone network, so that you can allow people who need help to get it?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Well, generally, again, the best thing we can do for -- in preparation for a hurricane is to build a foundational network, which we do at Verizon, that's built on reliability and redundancy.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "What happens if the storm is so strong that it starts smashing down your infrastructure in terms of towers and so on?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Well, it's a very worrying situation, Chad.", "docId": "110826pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 609}]